The review exercise’s main goal was to identify,
find, and fix the errors in this code. Whenever
we suspect errors in code, we should inspect
the code for possible obvious errors and use
any hints we get within the code editor
to find syntax errors. When in doubt,
run the code and see if errors come up. I will
run this code, and we see, in the traceback,
a syntax error on line 7. Syntax errors will
usually be identified before runtime errors.
We should fix one error at a time, as fixing one
error could fix multiple errors. The syntax error
is that we have a space between the f and the
opening quotation mark in this f-string. You
may recall that a space is not allowed there. So,
I will remove that space. When you fix an error,
you should run the code immediately to ensure the
fix works. I will rerun the code, and the syntax
error is gone, but there is a runtime error on
line 8. The error indicates that the equal sign
is not allowed as a symbol to align text. The
symbol should be less than 15 to get this value
to take 15 spaces. Even if you don’t remember the
exact phrasing of an alignment symbol, one way to
try to fix an error is to react directly to what
you’re being told. The equal sign is not allowed,
so we should remove it, which is what I will do.
I will rerun the code, and now the code works as
anticipated. Again, look over code for possible
errors, and run code when in doubt about errors,
as Python will help you find both syntax
and runtime errors. For logical errors,
you may need to test code in multiple ways to see
where the logic has gone wrong within the code.